What are we doing here?
I just want to make sure
that no one wants to hurt you.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHIEF] Hello, Sir Nabong?
Hello, Chief. I have something
to report.
It's good you called.
According to the forensic
report,
someone sabotaged Don Nato.
What?
How?
The yacht did not capsize
by accident.
It was on purpose
to destroy your clan.
I knew it.
Chief, I'll put you on speaker.
Chief, I have here with me
a distant relative of Don Nato.
She almost got into
an accident earlier.
Hello, Chief? I'm uh, I'm June!
Well...
a flower pot fell earlier.
I thought it was just a cat!
Be careful!
Most of them, they're close
to the family.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I think I know
who's the mastermind.
I already know who it is.
My brother told me.
Hello!
[IN UNISON] Attorney Zia!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]